对点对应问题说一点是有用的。
It's going to be useful to say a little bit more about the point correspondence problem.
在这里，我们再次看到了我们三角形物体的初始视图，在这里我们得到了最终的
Here we have again the initial view of our triangular object and here we have the final
我们的三角形对象的视图或所需的视图。
view, or the desired view, of our triangle object.
当点在图像平面中移动时，它们可以像这样和这样移动
When the points move in the image plane it's possible for them to move like this and this
是我们刚刚看过的例子。但这也有可能得分
is the example that we just looked at a moment ago. But it's also possible for the points
像这样移动，如果他们这样做那么对象的运动是三维的
to move like this and if they did that then the motion of the object in three dimensional
空间将变得更加复杂。它几乎要求物体翻转
space is going to be much more complex. It's almost going to require the object to flip
在三维世界里。
around in the three-dimensional world.
我们可以定义对应关系的另一种方式就是这样，它又涉及不同的方式
Another way we could define the correspondence is like this and again it involved a different
一种三维运动。
kind of three-dimensional motion.
最后我们可以让这种特殊的点在图像平面上移动。
And finally we could have this particular way of point moving on the image plane.
将黄点与红点相关联的每种不同方式将导致a
Each different way of associating a yellow dot with a red dot is going to result in a
三维世界中的不同运动。最终结果将是相同的
different motion in the three-dimensional world. The net result will be the same in
图像平面但实际的三维运动会有所不同。
the image plane but the actual three-dimensional motion will be different.